SERGE **CHURKIN**



289-501-7013



sergechurkin@gmail.com



/sergechurkin/



sergechurkin-ca



www.serge-web.com



Toronto, ON

CORE COMPETENCIES

Technical Skills:

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Sass
- Responsive design
- JavaScript
- API
- Github and Collaboration
- jQuery
- React and Firebase
- Node.js and Express

Additional Skills:

- Leadership
- Complex problem solving
- Project Management
- Customer service
- Communication, Presentations and Public Speaking

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, **Toronto | 2020**

- Web Development Immersive Certificate (Bootcamp)
- Accelerated Javascript
- Introduction to Web Development

Niagara College Canada, Niagara Falls, ON | 2016 - 2018

- International Business Management
- Tourism and Hospitality Management

PROFILE SUMMARY

Front End Web Developer who is passionate about building accessible and responsive web applications. I combine my background in large scale operations management and driving excellent customer care with my technical skillset to create user-friendly web experiences.

PROJECTS

Recipe Generator - JavaScript, API, jQuery, UX Design | View Live Poll It Together - React, Firebase, Github, Collaboration | View Live Tour Agency Inventory - React, Firebase | View Live Country Quiz - JavaScript, UX Design, SCSS | View Live

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Juno College of Technology Toronto, ON

Mar 2020 - Aug 2020

May 2018 - Jan 2020

Student

Fallsview Group of Hotels Niagara Falls, ON Night Audit Supervisor

- Improved processing of daily financial and balancing reports from 5 to 1.5 hrs
- Maximized revenue and ensured 101% hotel occupancy of with 200 rooms by monitoring reservations and updating rates
- Supervised and trained 2 auditors, shared best practices and trained booking system and reporting

Night Auditor

Aug 2016 - May 2018

- · Reconciled, audited and balanced accounts, prepared revenue reports in property with 600 rooms
- · Checked in guests, answered the calls and instant messages and ensured high standard of service

TEZ TOUR Thailand Phuket, Thailand **Regional Manager**

Feb 2015 - Feb 2016

- Oversaw inbound tourism operations in Phuket region, managed the team of 100 employees
- Developed strategies to implement sales targets and increased regional revenue by 20%
- Successfully maintained industry leadership image of the company among 200 local partner hotels and 25 tour suppliers

Quality Control Manager

Jul 2013 - Jan 2015

- · Improved the quality of service and advanced evaluation system in Phuket region with 200 daily arrivals
- · Developed and updated administrative policies and guidelines to maintain high quality of operations
- Obtained and tracked guest's feedback, resolved complaints and achieved satisfaction